Miss Thaiba Zaib

234 Cookham Road Maidenhead, Berkshire, SL6 7HL **Mobile:** 07541695746

Email address: thaibazaib@gmail.com

Profile

Hard working, enthusiastic and optimistic individual with a great sense of humour that excels at building lasting customer relationships in established, fast paced workplaces. My peers recognise me for my problem solving and multi-tasking, noting them as my strengths. Due to my passion for organising charity events outside of work, I am keen to build on my management and logistical skills.

Relevant Skills

- Determined individual who meets deadlines and is extremely organised.
- Problem solving & taking on new challenges.
- Excellent attention to detail.
- Good communication skills.
- Studied a range of topics during my BTEC Level 2 and Level 3 Diploma in Business including market research, business purposes, analysing cash-flow, different types of businesses and how to create a small business.

Work Experience

DHL Cross Border Solutions, Staines Junior Customer Support

(July 2020 - October 2020)

DHL is the world's leading logistics company. My role was based in the Cross-Border Solutions team and my responsibilities consisted of:

- Handle general Customer queries (via phone and email)
- Track parcel queries
- Generate weekly and monthly KPI Reporting

Lane4 Management Group Ltd, Maidenhead Client Services Co-ordinator

(September 2019 - July 2020)

Lane4 are experts in people performance, operating across a global network of clients to deliver people performance & leadership interventions. My role in this as Client Services Co-ordinator largely revolved around operational & logistical deliverables for a large-scale client.

In particular, my responsibilities included:

- Acting as a main point of contact for external & internal stakeholders.
- Assisting with the project plan maintaining daily trackers, scheduling, equipment & resourcing.
- Ensuring client SLAs & client policies are met.
- Organising virtual workshops as well as sending calendar invites to clients and associates.
- Booking venues & travel arrangements for consultants.
- POD contribution run unbilled report first Friday of every month and run planned Vs actual report for each Ops POD meeting.

Operations Assistant

(May 2018 - September 2019)

Prior to my promotion to Client Services Co-ordinator, I worked as an Operations Assistant; a fast-paced environment which required strong organisation and forward-thinking skills to ensure vital logistical deliverables were met. This involved:

- Liaising with client service managers/co-ordinators daily.
- Creating and sending out kits to a high standard and within the timescale.
- Booking flights/hotels/transfers for Consultants and Associates.
- Using Microsoft office skills by analysing data from evaluation forms & running "planned vs actual" reports.
- Liaising with different departments to understand their roles and how we all work together.

The Northview Group - Acenden Ltd, Maidenhead Service Advisor

(November 2016 - February 2018)

My role as a service provider at Acenden Ltd, a mortgage servicing company, involved providing exceptional customer service. My responsibilities were mainly to:

- Accurately recording information/events on to the administration systems which have been discussed via telephone.
- Go through income and expenditure to help rehabilitate customers and come to an affordable arrangement.
- Ensuring tasks/decisions taken place are made in line with Client Policy and Financial Regulations & Legislation.

Holiday Inn, Maidenhead Receptionist

(July 2015 - November 2016)

- Providing exceptional customer service at check in and check outs.
- Learned how to book reservations through various third parties.
- Exceeding target by up selling guests to becoming IHG reward members.

Odeon Cinema

Team Member (November 2013 - August 2015)

• Dealing with guest and providing excellent guest service.

Sports Direct

Casual Assistant (October 2011-2013)

- Stock replenishment of shoes, clothing and sports equipment.
- Working on tills

St Joseph's Church - Part-time Teaching Assistant (September 2008- July 2010)

• Helping the children in small groups and one-one to ensure that they understand the work that was set.

Vision Vehicle Solutions - Secretarial helper for work experience (June 2009)

Qualifications

September 2011- June 2014 (Reading College)

- BTEC National Diploma and Extended Diploma Level 3 [Pass, Pass, Merit]
- BTEC First Diploma in Business Level 2 [Merit]
- Functional Skills Level 2 English [Pass]

September 2005 – 2011 (Newlands Girls' School)

- Travel and Tourism & BTEC Retail Level 2
- GCSE Maths & English

Interests

- Trying out new activities, building my confidence (e.g. boxing and swimming).
- I enjoy travelling, experiencing different places and learning about cultures.
- Frequently assist with charity events (e.g. help for Syria) and convoys to third world countries.

References available upon request